Speaker 1: It's time!
Speaker 1: for controversial opinions which means it's time for Tom Bellingham to come in.
Speaker 0: If Max didn't fight the McLaren so hard he would have had a podium instead of George.
Speaker 1: So I'm gonna let you cook and then I'll see where I land.
Speaker 0: Okay so point one he lost the podium because of the badly timed virtual safety car which wasn't his fault and that's why George got ahead of him.
Speaker 0: The second point is I am convinced that some people just don't enjoy racing because heaven forbid that Max Verstappen actually defends his position and doesn't think about delta time.
Speaker 0: We need to to see more stuff like that because how do you let Lando through?
Speaker 0: it's very easy to kind of be like.
Speaker 0: oh well it helps with his Delta and all this kind of stuff and maybe it would have been quicker throughout the whole race.
Speaker 0: but then equally you know if there'd been a safety car or Lando gets a penalty or something later on you could be closer to him.
Speaker 0: so I don't think it should be a case of like drivers.
Speaker 0: oh off you go.
Speaker 0: McLarens are so much quicker.
Speaker 0: you know I don't want to see that and I don't think Max should have done that.
Speaker 1: I disagree with anyone that says that he messed up a potential p3.
Speaker 1: It was unlucky, the fact that the VSC came out, George Russell was able to benefit.
Speaker 1: We all have our own opinions on lap one, but when he was actually defending from Piastri, it was brilliant to watch.